gtrainers.com 2017-11-21

# Privacy Policy - GTrainers

**Information Collection and Use**

All materials posted on Gtrainers.com belong to their respective owners. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. We collect information from our users at several different points on our website.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s hard drive containing information about the user. Our website uses cookies to enhance the user's experience, often allowing a user to browse the site more quickly. The storage of such cookie is optional, and the user will still be able to use the website, with the exception of our member's area which requires a cookie to determine a member's login status. Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.

**Third Party Advertisers**

We work with third-party companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to our website in order to provide advertisements on this website, other websites and other forms of media about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please click here.

**Log Files and IPs**

IPs are logged in the server's log file which is used for administering the site. Log files contain no personally identifiable information.Under very rare circumstances, log files may be furnished to 3rd party advertisers for proof of traffic information. IPs are also stored within our message board area and are used to ban those users that do not comply with our message board rules.

**Sharing**

We will share traffic information (visitor counts) with partners and advertisers. None of this information contains personal information.

**Links**

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Gtrainers.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

**Notification of Changes**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users on our Homepage. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
